1plus2travel.com 2016-10-13

# 1 Plus 2 Travel

**What our Privacy Policy Covers** The Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on our website, [www.1plus2travel.com](http://www.1plus2travel.com/), [www.1plus2travel.co.uk](http://www.1plus2travel.co.uk/), [www.1plus2travel.net ](http://www.1plus2travel.net/), which is operated and owned by One Plus Two Travel Ltd (Registration No. 08639227) (“One Plus Two Travel”, “our”, “us” or “we”) with a registered office address at Suite 110, Axis Building, Maingate, Team Valley, Gateshead, NE11 0NQ, and when you use our services. We take our responsibilities for managing your personal data seriously and we operate in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and related legislation. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you use our website you will be regarded as having read and accepted this Privacy Policy. Please do not use this website or our services if you do not accept this Privacy Policy. When using our website, you may also use the services offered by other parties. In particular, payment systems are provided by third parties and the information you provide to facilitate payment is collected by such third parties and not One Plus Two Travel. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage. Please check the privacy practices of these other companies or persons (if any) to understand how they treat the personally identifiable information that you provide to them and contact them if you have any concerns. **Information Collection and Use by Us** We collect personally identifiable information when you create an account with us or register to receive email newsletters or other offers and promotions. Once you register with us, theoretically you are no longer anonymous to us. In addition, we automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address and the page you requested. Website usage information may also be collected automatically using cookies. We use information for three general purposes: to customise the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to contact you about specials and new products by sending you email alerts for new products, features, enhancements, special offers, contests, events of interest, and one-off marketing promotions. Such alerts may include marketing information about One Plus Two Travel or our subsidiaries. **Opt Out from Marketing Information** Any email we send to you will contain an easy automated unsubscribe link so that you can opt-out of the subscription. Simply follow the indications in the email. **Information Sharing and Disclosure by Us** We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. We will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people only when: 

  * We have your consent to share the information;
  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
  * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of us to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
  * We find that your actions on our web sites violate our Terms and Conditions, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.
  * We may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this privacy policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganisation of our business.

We will store any data which we collect from you on secure servers located within the United Kingdom. **Cookies** Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. We use the following cookies on our site: _Site Specific Cookies_ – We use a cookie to enable us to record whether you are logged in or out. These cookies are essential to the service that we provide to you. _Social Media Cookies_ – We may use social media sites such as [www.facebook.com](http://www.facebook.com/)  and [www.twitter.com](http://www.twitter.com/).  Social media widgets permit members of various social media websites the ability to like, share and bookmark various pages within [www.1plus2travel.com](http://www.1plus2travel.com/), [www.1plus2travel.co.uk](http://www.1plus2travel.co.uk/), [www.1plus2travel.net ](http://www.1plus2travel.net/), You can find out how to block these cookies for your particular browser by clicking "help" on your browser's menu or by visiting <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html>. Most web browsers allow some control of cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). _Web Stats_ \- These cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they have visited, the devices and browsers the visitor is using. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. **Ad Networks and “Re-Marketing”** We utilise third party vendors, including Google, to show ads for One Plus Two Travel on sites on the internet and we also permit advertising by Google Adwords on our website. Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website . Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively you can opt out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).) We’re not currently using DoubleClick’s re-marketing pixels, but it’s possible we will in the future in which case you can opt out of DoubleClick’s use of cookies by visiting the[DoubleClick opt-out page](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) or the [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). **Access to your information** You have a right to request a copy of the information we hold on you at any time. Please email us if you would like to receive a copy of this information [support@1plus2travel.com](mailto:support@1plus2travel.com). There may be a small charge for processing this request. **Other Websites** Our website may have links to other websites. This Privacy Policy only applies to this website and not those of other sites. You should therefore read the privacy policies of the other websites when you are using those sites. **Updates** This Privacy Policy is reviewed by us on a regular basis and may be updated from time to time. Please ensure that you are familiar with these changes. **February 2014.**
